Γ£à MongoDB Connected: localhost
Connected to MongoDB for metadata population
Clearing existing authors, publishers, categories, and reviews...
Building author documents...
Created 58 author documents.
Building publisher documents...
Created 336 publisher documents.
Building category documents...
Created 3049 category documents.
Creating review documents...
Creating review documents for 473 books...
Generating reviews for book 1/473: Learning React: Functional Web Development with React and Redux
Generating reviews for book 51/473: Breaking Point
Generating reviews for book 101/473: Project Hail Mary
Generating reviews for book 151/473: Effective Java
Generating reviews for book 201/473: Numerical simulation of a low emissions gas turbine combustor using KIVA-II
Generating reviews for book 251/473: The Lifecycle of Software Objects
Generating reviews for book 301/473: Freedom at Midnight
Generating reviews for book 351/473: Financial Accounting
Generating reviews for book 401/473: How Not to Die
Generating reviews for book 451/473: Um casamento arranjado
Created 1419 review documents.
Population complete.
